



(+598)98 531 101



gomezlucas712@gmail.com



Linkedin Lucas Gomez

#### **DEVELOPER**

Enthusiastic and self-taught software development student with a passion for creating web applications. Currently pursuing a FullStack Developer course on Udemy, honing skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, PHP, and SQL. Possesses knowledge gained in Focan España with a Data Base Analyst program, specializing in SQL, Apache, and MER. Committed to continuous learning and keeping up with industry trends. Strong problem-solving abilities and a team player mindset. Fluent in Spanish and conversational in English.

## **EDUCATION**

2022-Present

### **Bachelor in Computer Science**

ORT University Of Uruguay 1rst year student

### **Udemy Academy**

FullStack Developer (HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP and MySQL)

## **Udemy Academy**

Flutter (in progress)

March 2022- November 2022

### Focan España

Data Base Analyst (SQL,NoSQL,FireBase, Apache, MER)

# **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS
- JS, NodeJS, React,
- PHP, SQL, AJAX
- Figma
- Dart (Flutter)
- CI/CD

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native

English: C2

# **EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Full-Stack Developer Last Project: Real Estate Website

- Duration: May 2022 August 2022
- Collaborated to create a dynamic real estate website.
- Implemented backend functionality with Node.js to manage property listings and user inquiries.
- Integrated Google Maps API for interactive property location display.
- Optimized website performance.

#### Advisor-Manager

Asesoría Vic2 | July 2022 - November 2022

Customer Support, advice to clients with government procedures

#### **Delivery Driver**

Zona Logistica | December 2020 - January 2022

Distribution of mobile phones, medicines and miscellaneous items.I had employees in charge.